=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الصغير للإمبراطور الشيطاني =
=Episode 20=
= الحلقة 20 =
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
At ease.
في سهولة.
You have to ask
عليك أن تسأل
what she thinks.
ما تعتقده.
No need to ask.
لا حاجة لطرح سؤال.
I say yes.
اقول نعم.
Yueying.
يويينج.
Young Master and Ms. Chuchu arranged this.
رتب السيد الشاب والسيدة تشوتشو هذا.
Are you not interested in the Second Prince at all?
هل أنت غير مهتم بالأمير الثاني على الإطلاق؟
I...
أنا...
I don't know either.
لا اعرف ايضا.
Why don't you give him an opportunity?
لماذا لا تعطيه فرصة؟
Our ranks are very different.
صفوفنا مختلفة جدا.
Besides,
بجانب،
the men from the royal family are unfaithful.
رجال العائلة المالكة هم غير مخلصين.
Who can guarantee that
من يستطيع أن يضمن ذلك
this isn't just a momentary novelty to him?
هذه ليست مجرد لحظة جديدة بالنسبة له؟
Who cares about the ranks?
من يهتم بالرتب؟
Yueying.
يويينج.
You're like a sister to me.
أنت مثل أخت لي.
You're more than enough for Li Wuming.
أنت أكثر من كافٍ لـ Li Wuming.
As for if he's sincere,
أما إذا كان صادقًا ،
we shall try it out.
سنجربه.
Thank you for being sincere, Your Highness.
شكرا لك على صدقك يا صاحب السمو.
I...
أنا...
will not disappoint you.
لن يخيب ظنك.
This is a sudden twist.
هذا تطور مفاجئ.
Am I dreaming?
هل أنا في حلم؟
I'm not dreaming.
أنا لا أحلم.
This is real.
هذا حقيقي.
No way. I don't agree.
مستحيل.  أنا لا أوافق.
Unless I'm dead,
إلا إذا كنت ميتا ،
I'll never approve of this marriage.
لن أوافق على هذا الزواج.
Your Majesty, say something.
جلالة الملك ، قل شيئًا.
Alright now.
حسنا الآن.
It seems the royal family
يبدو أن العائلة المالكة
will have a wedding soon.
سيقيم حفل زفاف قريبا.
Wuyou, listen to me.
Wuyou ، استمع إلي.
Speak up. I'm going to see Chuchu.
تكلم.  أنا ذاهب لرؤية تشوتشو.
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
Mother cried and threatened me with death.
بكت أمي وهددتني بالموت.
She made noise until late night.
لقد أحدثت ضوضاء حتى وقت متأخر من الليل.
She insists that I call off the marriage.
تصر على أن ألغي الزواج.
That's your mother.
هذه والدتك.
Figure out something yourself.
اكتشف شيئًا بنفسك.
You...
أنت...
You can deal with her better than I do.
يمكنك التعامل معها أفضل مني.
Although Mother looks
على الرغم من أن الأم تبدو
very formidable usually,
هائل جدا عادة ،
she doesn't even care about my father,
هي حتى لا تهتم بوالدي ،
in fact in her heart
في الحقيقة في قلبها
she cares the most about you.
هي تهتم بك أكثر من غيرها.
Oh no, Young Master.
أوه لا ، سيد الشباب.
Chuchu is taken away by the empress' subordinates.
يتم أخذ Chuchu من قبل مرؤوسي الإمبراطورة.
What?
ماذا؟
Wuyou.
Wuyou.
Your Majesty, Ms. Chuchu is here.
جلالة الملك ، السيدة تشوتشو هنا.
Let her in.
دعها تدخل.
Your Majesty, are you looking for me?
جلالة الملك ، هل تبحث عني؟
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
You're not greeting me
أنت لا تستقبلني
on your kneels.
على ركبتيك.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
تحياتي جلالة الملك.
Qiao Chuchu.
تشياو تشوتشو.
I've been kind to you.
لقد كنت لطيفا معك.
Why are you always against me?
لماذا انت دائما ضدي؟
Your Majesty, what does it mean?
جلالة الملك ، ماذا يعني ذلك؟
My admiration for you
اعجابي بك
is as endless as the surging water of Yangtze
لا نهاية لها مثل المياه المتدفقة لنهر اليانغتسي
and overflowing like the water of the Yellow River.
وتفيض مثل مياه النهر الأصفر.
Wanton!
وحشي!
Stop talking nonsense here.
توقف عن الحديث عن الهراء هنا.
I can stop caring
يمكنني التوقف عن الاهتمام
about Li Wuyou.
حول Li Wuyou.
But Wuming
لكن Wuming
is my only hope.
هو أملي الوحيد.
I don't allow anyone to ruin him.
لا أسمح لأحد أن يفسده.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
It's a great thing that the Second Prince
إنه لأمر رائع أن الأمير الثاني
can be with the person he loves.
يمكن أن يكون مع الشخص الذي يحبه.
How would that ruin him?
كيف سيخربه ذلك؟
As the saying goes,
على رأي القول،
you can demolish 10 temples, but never destroy a marriage.
يمكنك هدم 10 معابد ، لكن لا يمكنك تدمير الزواج.
The couples who have signed the Marriage Book
الأزواج الذين وقعوا على دفتر الزواج
and engraved their names on the Three Lives Stone
ونقشوا أسمائهم على حجر الحياة الثلاث
are brought together by fate that's cultivated for hundreds of years.
يتم جمعها معًا من خلال القدر الذي تمت زراعته لمئات السنين.
Your Majesty.
جلالة الملك.
Why are you being so stubborn?
لماذا أنت عنيد جدا؟
A young lady with a sharp tongue.
شابة لسانها حاد.
No wonder Li Wuyou
لا عجب لي وويو
is so fascinated by you.
هو مفتون جدا بك.
Sadly, I don't buy this.
للأسف ، أنا لا أشتري هذا.
Servant.
خادم.
Tear her mouth.
مزق فمها.
Yes, Your Majesty.
نعم يا صاحب الجلالة.
Let's talk.
لنتحدث.
Don't use violence.
لا تستخدم العنف.
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪